[Music]
you know President Obama didn't live
through September 11 I did the president
didn't live through September 11th what
are you saying he was born 13 years ago
then is that why they wanted to see his
birth
certificate no idea oh so I guess it's
not that he was born in Kenya it was
that he was born in October of 2001 I
guess let's imagine Obama's Jay-Z and
Juliana's Vanilla Ice let's say what
should what should he do about vanilla
well I don't you know it's kind of
similar like rat beef and political beef
it's a beef I just feel like political
beef is a little more violent
right your other two Amigos yeah Chevy
Chase and Steve Martin yeah okay are
facing El Guapo firing squad only
because he has a a little baby child
taking too long I'd have to pick Steve
because Chevy's children are grown and
therefore but I would also pick hey
America Larry Wilmore here if you like
the nightly show on Comedy Central like
us on Facebook too just don't poke me I
do not like being poked you can Candy
Crush me